Guide to the Sapolsky and Slobodien Architecture collection 1948-1985 PR 439
New-York Historical Society
- Series III: Longchamps, 1959-1966
  This series contains correspondence, drawings, permits, and invoices related to Sapolsky and Slobodien's work for the New York City restaurant chain Longchamps
  - 59-25 Longchamps Fifth Avenue and 34th Street, NYC, 1959 (Offsite-box 9)
  - 59-44 Longchamps 1019 Madison Avenue, NYC, 1959 (Offsite-box 9)
  - 59-59 Longchamps Restaurant 624 Madison Avenue, NYC, 1959 (Offsite-box 9)
  - 59-66 Longchamps 1117 Third Avenue, NYC, 1959 (Offsite-box 9)
  - 59-72 Longchamps 1450 Broadway, NYC, 1959 (Offsite-box 9)
  - 60-31 Longchamps Restaurant 55 Fifth Avenue, NYC, 1960 (Offsite-box 9)
  - 60-26 Longchamps 253 Broadway, NYC, 1960 (Offsite-box 9)
  - 60-66 Longchamps East 49th Street, NYC, 1960-1963 (Offsite-box 9)
  - 63-10 Longchamps 253 Broadway, NYC, 1963 (Offsite-box 9)
  - 63-31 Longchamps Empire State Building, NYC, 1963 (Offsite-box 9)
  - 64-13 Longchamps 42nd Street and Lexington Avenue, NYC, 1964 (Offsite-box 9)
  - 64-16 Longchamps Restaurant 55 Fifth Avenue, NYC, 1964 (Offsite-box 9)
  - 64-18 Longchamps 253 Broadway, NYC, 1964 (Offsite-box 9)
  - 64-21 Longchamps 59th Street, NYC, 1964 (Offsite-box 10)
  - 64-21 Longchamps 635 Madison Avenue, NYC, 1964 (Offsite-box 10)
  - 65-27 Jan Mitchell Longchamps 423 Madison Avenue, NYC, 1965 (Offsite-box 10)
  - 65-30 Longchamps New Offices 635 Madison Avenue, NYC, 1965 (Offsite-box 10)
  - 65-A-33 Longchamps Penn Plaza, NYC, 1965 (Offsite-box 10)
  - 65-A-59 Longchamps 79th Street, NYC, 1965 (Offsite-box 10)
  - 65-A-63 Longchamps 41st Street and Broadway NYC, 1965 (Offsite-box 10)
  - 66-28 Longchamps 253 Broadway NYC, 1966 (Offsite-box 10)
  - 66-60 Longchamps 34th Street-350 Fifth Avenue NYC, 1966 (Offsite-box 10)
- Series IV: Luchow's Restaurant, 1952-1971
  This series contains correspondence, blueprints, drawings, permit applications, specifications, inspection reports, and invoices related to Sapolsky and Slobodien's work for the New York City restaurant Luchow's.
  - Correspondence, 1952-1955 (Offsite-box 11)
  - 56-11, Luchow's, 110-112 East 14th Street, 1957-1958 (Offsite-box 11)
  - 58-6 108 East 14th Street, 110-112 East 14th Street, 1958-1961 (Offsite-box 11)
  - 61-13, Luchow's, 110-112 East 14th Street, 1961-1964 (Offsite-box 11)
  - 62-24, Luchow's, 110-112 East 14th Street, 1962-1965 (Offsite-box 11)
  - 62-84 Roof Structure, 1962-1968 (Offsite-box 11)
  - 66-26 Contract Drawings and Specs, 1958-66 (Offsite-box 11)
  - 66-26 Meeting Notes, Correspondence, Invoices, Concrete Test Reports, 1966-1969 (Offsite-box 11)
  - 66-A-26 108 East 14th Street, NYC, 1961-1966 (Offsite-box 11)
  - 67-42 Miscellaneous, 1967 (Offsite-box 11)
  - 68-23 108 East 14th Street, 2nd Floor Break-through, 1968 (Offsite-box 11)
  - 68-31 Bar and Entrance, 1968 (Offsite-box 11)
  - 70-33 Inspection and Report, 1970-1971 (Offsite-box 11)
- Series V: Other Buildings, 1948-1971
  This series contains correspondence, blueprints, drawings, permit applications, and invoices related to various stores and commerical sites designed and renovated by Sapolsky and Slobodien.
  - Blueprints - Various Projects, 1948-1971 (Offsite-box 8)
  - Presentation Drawings (6)- Various Projects, 1948-1953 (Offsite-box 13)
  - 49-21 Ansonia Shop, 5th Avenue, 1949-1951 (Offsite-box 12)
  - 60-5, Arthur Brown, 2 West 46th Street, 1960 (Offsite-box 12)
  - 65-71, Arthur Brown, Grand Central Artists' Materials, 3 East 40th Street, NYC, 1965 (Offsite-box 12)
  - 67-A-4, Arthur Brown, 2 West 46th Street, 1967 (Offsite-box 12)
  - 70-A K&K Electric, 535 8th Avenue, 1970 (Offsite-box 12)
  - 71-A-23, Ambassador Construction, 380 Madison Avenue, 18th Floor, 1971 (Offsite-box 12)
  - 71-24 Ambassador Construction, 919 Third Avenue, 2nd Floor, 1971 (Offsite-box 12)
  - 71-25 Ambassador Construction, 888 Seventh Avenue, 44th Floor, 1971 (Offsite-box 12)
  - 71-28 Kimmelman Home, 33 East 70th Street, Penthouse, 1971 (Offsite-box 12)
  - 71-29 Resnick Institute of Technology, 7323 20th Avenue, Brooklyn, 1971 (Offsite-box 12)
  - 71-32 Sam's Ninth Avenue Meat Market, 593 Ninth Avenue, 1971 (Offsite-box 12)
  - 71-14 Tree Mark Shoe Stores, 38th & 58th Streets, 1971 (Offsite-box 12)
  - 71-A-16 Town School Nursery, 538 East 76th Street, 1971 (Offsite-box 12)
  - 71-9 48 West 48th Street, Front Repair, 1971 (Offsite-box 12)
  - 71-12 Bookson, 35 Fourth Avenue, Brooklyn, 1971 (Offsite-box 12)
  - 71-A-13 151 West 40th Street, 7th Floor, 1971 (Offsite-box 12)
  - 71-2 Linder, 408 Dewitt Avenue, Brooklyn, 1971 (Offsite-box 12)
  - 71-6 Bergman, 62 West 39th Street, 6th Floor, 1970-1971 (Offsite-box 12)
  - 71-7 Childcare Center, Brooklyn, 1971 (Offsite-box 12)
  - 71-35 Stark's Restaurant 1001 Madison Avenue, 1971 (Offsite-box 12)